question_data = [
{"question":"When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The color orange is named after the fruit.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The Sun rises from the North.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Bulls are attracted to the color red.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"One of Donald Trump&#039;s 2016 Presidential Campaign promises was to build a border wall between the United States and Mexico.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Slovakia is a member of European Union-","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"French is an official language in Canada.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]